Hello everyone, I am Lydia from Clou, a Chinese company.
Today, my colleagues and I will introduce the new features of Clou 6.0.
In the following five parts, we will explain the new features of Clou 6.0,
such as the model, rendering, materials, and functional optimization.
First of all, we will introduce the new features of Clou 6.0.
The new features of Clou 6.0 are divided into the following six points.
Please take a look.
First of all, we will introduce our automatic rendering,
instrument, and tool.
The tool is now in our 3D tool column.
Why is it in the 3D tool column and 2D?
Because we automatically recognize the identification of a relationship through our point of arrangement.
We have to arrange our panels in the correct position.
For example, I choose the front of our shirt and put it in the point of arrangement in the front chest.
Then put our scarf
in the point of arrangement in the front.
The collar is placed in the point of arrangement in the neck.
The sleeves are placed in the point of arrangement in the arm.
The small sleeve cuff is placed on our wrist.
The back piece is placed on our back.
After arranging the whole outfit,
we can click on the tool in the point of arrangement.
Our automatic recognition tool.
Then we can click on the tool in the point of arrangement.
Okay, you can see that our sewing line can now be automatically added.
Let's simulate it and see its effect.
You can see that there is no problem with its sewing relationship.
There is a sewing on some details.
Let me make up our sewing line a little bit.
Then we will soon have the whole outfit sewn.
Okay, you can take a look.
Then our automatic recognition tool.
After that, you can use our automatic recognition tool
to recognize our single-layer outfit,
dress group, and some parts on the outfit.
For the time being, it can not be applied to makeup and layered outfits.
It can save you a lot of recognition time.
What needs to be emphasized again is that our automatic recognition
is to identify their recognition relationship
and to identify their sewing relationship.
So the correct point of arrangement is very necessary.
The next one I would like to introduce to you
is the function of our survey code.
This function is also one of the highlights of our 6.0.
It is in our mode.
You can see that there is a new mode called survey code here.
Now I open a file with code information.
After opening it,
we can open the code information in our 2D window.
You can see that it has a three-digit code number of an outfit.
Now we switch to the code bar of our object window.
You can see that there is now an image card
that matches the virtual model on the right side of our size.
Then our image card is to match the corresponding image card
to our three-digit outfit.
This image card is to match the corresponding image card
This image card is to match the corresponding virtual model to our three-digit outfit.
Let's update it.
Then there is a list of numbers that match our model.
The first S number has been matched to our default model.
Let's click to save the 3D state.
Switch to our next code.
Then match the model of this number.
After matching,
we need to simulate this outfit a little bit.
OK.
After matching, we turn off the simulation.
Then click to save the 3D state.
The operation of this number below is the same.
When switching numbers,
it is recommended that you switch the number next to it.
This way, the simulation will be more stable
because the number of changes will be smaller.
OK.
We have already simulated the third number.
Click to save the 3D state.
In this way,
we can check the three-digit number in the same picture
under the simulation model.
If we unlock this picture,
it can be examined in a single window.
We still lock it first.
Here is a different switching effect of our picture layout.
Then you can reset and full screen.
Then here is a high and wide ratio of our drawing.
You can set it according to different needs.
Of course, you can also save our picture.
Here is a picture that I saved for you in advance.
In this picture,
you can see that it is a positioning of a hard flower.
So in our three numbers,
the position of a hard flower
can be clearly seen here.
Next, I will introduce you to the main update of our plant texture.
It is divided into two parts.
One is our text editor.
The other is our hard flower.
This is also a very important content in this update.
First of all, I will introduce you to the function of our text editor.
First of all, I will open our file.
The function of the text editor
is that it can give us a multiple layer pattern,
a layer pattern,
to make a quick stack design
to form our text.
Let me turn off the text editor display.
You can see that there is a new button
next to the text below our plant.
Let's click on this button.
The interface of our text editor will appear.
In the middle,
we can preview our text.
This is the window of the text effect.
The top is a high and wide value of this single text.
We can change this value
to change the text of our single loop.
Next is a layer of this text.
We can add a lot of layer text here
to do the design.
Here is a property that can be edited.
Let's add our text now.
It is defaulted to be placed on the top of our text.
We can select it
and then in our preview window
to shrink and enlarge it,
and then rotate its direction
to make it bigger.
Then here,
we can set it to be repeated,
flat,
or extended to the other side.
This kind of text effect
is OK.
Then I will add another layer.
I will shrink this lemon
and put it in the middle of our two layers.
I can change the mixing mode of its pattern.
I can change its color
to let it penetrate the base pattern.
Next,
I will add another pattern.
When it comes in,
shrink it a little,
put it on our corner,
and extend it to the other side.
Make it a little bigger.
In this way,
I have designed such a pattern soon.
Let's apply it.
After application,
you can see that this pattern
has been saved
in the window of our pattern.
When we click to browse,
we can see that it is now saved
in our folder.
We can add another pattern
in the color window,
and then open the second pattern
of the text editor.
You can see that
in the text editor of the second pattern,
it will also keep
the elements of the previous design.
We can do a redesign
of the same group of design elements.
For example,
I put the bottom of this blue
for a fill.
It becomes a white bottom.
Then this pattern
is resized
by its size and angle.
Make it a little bigger.
Then change its color
to our red.
Then confirm.
Then change the width
to our 800.
You can see that its single loop
has now changed its width.
Of course,
we put this pattern
in the middle.
Then put this on top.
Change its blending mode
to normal.
So our second pattern
is already designed.
Let's click on the application.
In our flag color,
update it.
You can see that
in our flag color,
you can quickly design
two different patterns
with the same group of design elements.
The next thing I will explain to you
is our
print function.
When you need to
fill in a pattern
with a pattern
that is different
from the font material,
you can use this function.
For example,
I have a new button
next to my account
here
called
add print.
Then I will
add our
new print
to it.
After adding it,
you can see that
our new button
is already filled
with the whole
surface of our cloth.
It is not in it.
Then we can
change the material
of this print
.
For example,
I changed this print
to our
metal material.
Then you can
switch to its
repeat type.
There are three different
repeat types
for you to choose from.
Of course,
it also has
its own
text editor.
We can design
this print
layer
for this print.
So,
this is
the main
update
of our
plant
text
.
I believe
the two tools
of the text editor
and print
can make it
very convenient
for everyone
to do
the work of
text design.
Next,
I will introduce
the main update
of our
plant property.
Now,
Cloud 6.0
is using
our PBR
workflow.
What is PBR?
PBR is
Physically Based Rendering,
a rendering process.
It is a
kind of
color rendering
and rendering
technology
that can
show
the material
material
more
realistically.
Now,
let me
show you
the transparent
and metal
images
added
to our
plant property
editor.
Now,
let me
show you
the transparent
image
in our
software.
Now,
I am going to
apply
a transparent image
on the first
piece of
material.
You can see
that our
transparent image
is now
added to
the bottom
of our
transparency.
There is a transparent
image,
can you see it?
Then,
we drag
our transparent
image
directly in.
After dragging
it in,
you can see
its default mode
is our
RGB mode.
You can see
its transparency.
There is a
different level
of transparency
in the pattern
of our
bird.
The transparent
image of
this RGB mode
is a completely
opaque gray
image.
Then,
the closer
to the white
place,
the more
opaque,
the closer
to the black
place,
the more
transparent.
This is an effect
applied
on a plant
in the
second piece of
our
material.
We first
switch to the
software
to apply
another
alpha
transparent image
to our
second piece of
material.
After dragging
it in,
its mode
is changed
to our
alpha.
After
moving
it,
you can see
that the
effect of
this transparent
image
is not
transparent
at all.
In the
picture,
my bird
pattern
is set to
be
100%
opaque.
The background
is 30%
transparent.
So,
the effect
is like
this.
Next,
I will
introduce
our
metal
image.
Let's
go back
to our
software.
Let's
apply
our
reflection.
Under
this reflection,
there is a
metal
degree
and our
metal
image is
our
new
one.
When I
just
asked
the question,
there was
a guest
asking
about
this
content,
so you can
listen carefully.
Let's
drag
our
metal
material.
We can
add
a highlight
image
to
use
to set
our
reflection
area.
Adjust the
intensity
so that
we can
make a
partial
tan
effect.
Then
we
add
our
texture
image
and
you can
see
this is
an explanation
of PPT.
Our
metal image
is also
a gray
picture.
The closer
to the
white
place,
the more
metallic
it is,
the stronger
it is.
The closer
to the
black
place,
the more
metallic
it is,
the weaker
it is.
We
can
add
the
texture
to
our
material.
We can
imagine that
our
original
material layer
is at
the bottom
and our
material
is at
the top.
Our
material
is actually
covered
with a
material
film
on our
material.
Let's
see
how to
change
this
material
into
iridensis.
After
changing
it,
we can't
see the
effect
in the
3D window
because
it has
to
start
the
dyeing.
You
can
see
the
dyeing
effect
in the
dyeing
window.
Under
the color
parameter,
we will
do a
simple
introduction
through
PPT.
The first
is the
dyeing effect.
The most
influential
is the
dyeing
strength
in the
middle.
You can
see
these
three
pictures.
The first
picture shows
that
the
dyeing
strength
is
higher
than the
wear
and tear
strength
.
The second
picture shows
that
the
dyeing
strength
is
lower
than the
wear
strength.
The
color
is
lighter
than
the
wear
strength.
The
When you want to make a random change to our five colors,
you can use this parameter.
It will move a certain value on our color ring
to change our five colors at the same time.
The last one is the weight.
This defines the ratio of our plant layer and the change layer.
When set to 0, it represents our plant layer.
When set to 1, it represents our change layer.
One is 0.1 and the other is 0.8.
This is the effect of the change layer.
Next, I will introduce the important update on plant properties.
Before 6.0, we have cooperated with vZoom
and we can import the xPath file that it has scanned
and import our text image, highlight image, and hair line image
to show our material.
In 6.0,
with the expansion of digitalization and 3D technology,
we have cooperated with many leading companies.
First, we have Substance.
Substance is an Adobe company's
art production tool software.
It includes our painter and designer.
We can now integrate their S-B-S-A-R format file.
Let me show you.
This file is a
program logic file.
It can be set according to our program design.
Its self-definition properties are different.
For example, I drag in a piece of S-B-S-A-R file.
Then you can see its lower right corner
has a Substance logo.
And its properties will automatically switch to our Substance.
Then below,
we click on its self-definition properties.
This plant is
made up of the base pattern,
the top decoration bead,
and the embroidery.
We can directly change
each layer's self-definition properties.
For example,
we can change the color of its properties.
We can change its base pattern to a bright green color.
Or we can change the top decoration bead,
this gray decoration bead,
to a red one.
You can see that it can immediately
change these elements.
Because it is a program logic.
We can show you its effect.
For example,
you can see that it shows the texture of the plant.
And the texture of the metal decoration bead on it
is very realistic.
In addition to Substance,
we also have a
S-B-S-A-R-F
In addition to Substance,
we also have
the ASF file created by the TSC Tax System of the Israeli company.
This file is similar to the X-Tax file we had before.
It can also be scanned through their system
to get our text,
hair,
and so on.
Then, it is packed and loaded into our system at a time.
For example,
I am now loading the
ASF file
which is
a
naked
laser.
Let's scan it
and take a look.
Then,
the property editor
has been opened.
As you can see,
its texture,
hair line,
calligraphy,
transparency,
and
our highlight,
resolution,
have been added at a time.
Then,
it may take a certain amount of time to scan.
What you can notice is
that
there is another one
about our ColorDigital.
This is a German
digital cloud platform
asset management company.
They made a cloud platform
for DMX.
If you use their service,
you can also drag the ASF file on the platform
directly into the cloud to use.
You need to pay attention to what I just introduced
and the current DMX Cloud of ColorDigital.
These are all ASF file formats.
You can also use them to scan
and verify that the SD card was scanned correctly.
OK,
this should be enough.
You can take a look
at this message.
Next,
what I will introduce to you
is a feature
of our
Auto Virtual Model Transfer function.
Many of our
enterprise users
scan our 3D model
to use this web model
on their own.
In the version of the cloud 5.0,
we support
self-control
to convert our self-reliant model into our Cloud model.
Now in 6.0, we have greatly optimized this function.
We can automatically convert our model into three different forms
to meet everyone's different needs.
Let's take a look at how to use it.
Let's build our file.
In front of our virtual model, there is an automatic virtual model.
Let's open it.
After opening it, let's open our 3D model file first.
It will prompt us to recommend a model file with a hand-drawn pose.
Then find our OmniGelid file and import it.
After importing it,
we will enter its gender.
Then select it.
After selecting it,
we can see three different types of output below.
The common point is that they all bind our Google.
The difference is that the first model of Cloud skin type
can attach our Cloud skin to the surface of our model,
but its body shape remains the original file.
Then the second one only binds Google,
that is, it only binds Google.
Other data remains unchanged.
The third one,
the model with a size that can be edited,
is also based on the binding Google.
It also matches the closest model data to this model in our Cloud.
So its size can be edited.
When we are exporting,
we can select a single or multiple output.
Let's choose a storage path.
For example, I will save it on the desktop.
Then click Save.
Then we can click Transfer.
The transfer process takes a few minutes.
So here I will show you first.
Open a file that I have already transferred in advance.
Let me show you.
You can see that there are now four models in this file.
I open this one.
You can see that the first one is our original file.
It is now bound to Google.
The last three are the ones we transferred.
They are bound to our Google.
The difference is just as I said just now.
The first one is attached to our Cloud skin type.
But the size is the same as the original model.
The third model can be edited.
We can open our virtual model editor.
You can see that after opening it,
only the surface of the third model has this kind of measured virtual line display.
Then we go to the first one or the second one.
It will remind us that we can't edit it.
This function is a function of our automatic virtual model transfer.
The next one I will introduce to you is our secondary surface scattered.
What is secondary surface scattered?
This is a material that is semi-transparent on the surface such as human skin, candles, and trees.
When the light shines on the surface of this material,
it will not only reflect,
but it will penetrate the surface of our object and scatter it.
It makes the surface of our object look semi-transparent.
You can see that in this picture,
the model on the left on the right,
it is recognized by our光 material.
And then the one on the left is the secondary surface scattered.
You can see the difference in this place of the ear.
It is a more transparent feeling.
It looks more real.
Now we are in our software.
In this video, I will show you this material.
I will use a set of numbers as an example to give you an explanation.
This set of numbers, I will change it.
After selecting it, I will change its material type.
In this place, its material type is called skin.
Because in our blog, this material is usually applied to our model's skin.
So we call it skin skin.
And then we are in our skin.
And then we open it in our rendering window.
It may take some time to render.
Let's take a look at the parameters of this material first.
What are there now?
Under our secondary surface scattered,
you can see that it has a combination density ratio
and some parameters of three layers of color.
We now switch to our PPT to give you an explanation.
There is also a picture that has already been shown here.
You can see that this small horse made of matte material
is very solid.
It's not transparent.
And the secondary surface scattered has a sense of transparency.
The first parameter is our combination.
This value is from 0 to 1.
The larger the value, the stronger the effect of the scattered.
That is, this place will be more transparent.
And then the second one is our density ratio.
The density ratio shows the transparency of this object.
The smaller the density ratio, the more transparent the object is.
So it looks like this.
The more transparent the effect, the better.
What about the following color attribute?
It is divided into three layers of color.
It is a mixture effect.
I took away the pink color on the surface of these two pieces.
Just go to the surface layer.
That is, the three layers of color inside.
Then the first picture of this small horse.
It is a mixture of red and green.
Under the color model of our RGB.
After the red and green are mixed together, it is yellow.
So it shows a yellowish effect.
You can also add our color picture.
To control its color.
The effect of the scattered.
You can see that the pattern is scattered like this.
If you don't understand this part.
It doesn't matter.
Because when we are in the application.
When we change to this material.
Its default parameter.
It is suitable for most of our model's skin materials.
So you can use it directly.
If you are interested.
We will post a detailed push later.
In our WeChat.
You can do a detailed review.
The next time.
I will leave it to my colleague Nicole.
Let her continue to introduce you.
Thank you.
Hello everyone.
I'm the designer.
From Shanghai Colour Company.
I will introduce the four remaining parts.
Model part.
display part, material part and function optimization part.
First, let's take a look at the mode part.
In the mode part, we added two new modes.
In addition to the view mode introduced earlier,
we also added a mode here, UV Editor Mode,
as well as some updates to the hard disk release mode and the color mode.
UV Editor Mode is used to import the clothes that have been made
to other 3D software for the later special effects.
Let's open a file here.
Switch it to UV Editor Mode.
This is our UV Editor window.
The upper left corner can be switched to different images,
such as text, graphics, metal, and so on.
The upper right corner can be kept
as its grid UV window.
And it can be kept
as a different braided text.
Braided text has text, metal, graphics, and so on.
This is our UV Editor Mode.
In our hard disk release mode,
we also made some updates here.
In the same way, we will use a file to show you.
This is a string of four dragons.
It contains code information.
Here we will switch it to the hard disk release mode.
I will arrange all the files.
This is a function of our 5.2 pudding version.
Let me introduce it to you.
Here we can arrange multiple clothes.
And we can set the keys between the files.
The keys between the files are a new function of our 6.0.
And we can arrange all the numbers.
Because this clothing contains code information,
I can arrange it here.
Then run it.
It takes a little time.
I put a seal on this version.
After running it, we can check its number.
Switch it to the color mode.
The color mode of our interface has been optimized.
Now the same material has been classified.
For example, the plant type, the sticker type, and the folk type.
If I want to change the color of this group of yellow,
I can directly right-click here and select all the same colors.
I can change a new color for it.
If I want to change the color of this group of gray,
because it is gray of different degrees,
I can select the first gray here,
press the Shift key, and then select the last one.
I can also change a new color for it.
If I want to change the color of the same name material,
I can select the first one here,
press the Ctrl key, and then select the second one.
I can also change a new color for it.
This is an update of our color mode.
Next, I would like to introduce the rendering part.
In the rendering part, we added some new features.
For example, the rendering display of the style chart,
as well as the full-fledged frame,
the preservation and application of the rendering properties.
Let's open a new file.
The style chart rendering shows that
in the second part of our 3D window,
let's open the second one here.
It can display different lines.
For example, the outline line, the border line,
the inner line, and the nose line.
These lines can adjust its outline,
and the small eyes behind the eyes
can be hidden by it.
Now my inner line is hidden.
I can open it.
And I can change the color of these lines.
The color of the costume can also be changed.
You can also fill in the texture of the costume.
You can use the original texture of the costume.
You can also adjust the overall brightness of the costume.
After adjustment,
we can save it through the quick photo.
Let's take a look at the effect we saved before.
This is the effect of the style chart rendering.
Next, I would like to introduce
the all-in-one effect.
You may have had such a question before.
My 3D window costume is done.
When I want to render,
the effect of my 3D window is OK.
But the effect of my 3D window
is not so satisfactory.
Here,
we have introduced a new function in 6.0.
In our style chart,
there is a texture of the costume.
Let's adjust it here.
Let's render it at the same time.
You can see that
the texture of the costume here
has only changed the effect of our style chart window.
It does not change the effect of our 3D window.
So this function can meet the needs of both.
And when we render,
we need to adjust the texture of the picture,
the texture of the lighting,
and the texture of the lens.
The previous version
can save each individual texture.
We have introduced a new function in 6.0.
It can save all the texture settings
of my style window with one click.
Here,
you can rename the file here
to a style chart.
You can save it.
Here,
I add a new costume.
Let's render it at the same time.
The result of this style chart
is the default effect of my style chart window.
Here,
we can load the style chart properties
that we have already saved.
In the same file,
there is a style chart property here.
You can load all the style settings
of the style chart window with one click.
Let's render it at the same time.
This function is mainly used to
when you render other costume settings,
you don't need to adjust the settings anymore.
When you render other costume settings,
Next
I want to introduce you
our material part.
There are five little things to update.
The first thing is the sticker.
The second is to edit the text file and
the virtual model has been converted into a sub-model.
In addition,
YKKě has been added to the default.
And there is also theлыm
and the Cheron Technology.
First,
let's take a look at the sticker.
Here
you can see
in the elaborated template,
In the past, when you were drawing a sticker on a board, you usually needed to add two stickers to two boards to adjust its position.
Now, we can choose the sticker here.
Then, in the property editor, we added a number to open it.
Then, my sticker can automatically cross two boards.
And here you can see that there is a sticker in front of our chest.
And there is a name line on the sticker.
Here, we open the rendering.
Let's run the rendering.
As you can see, the sticker in front of the chest and the name line are not displayed.
This is because this piece of fabric is made of wool.
It is made with a replacement.
It has a replacement degree.
So here we can check the replacement degree of this piece of fabric.
The replacement degree of this piece of fabric is 2.
So, we added a new function to 6.0.
We can choose the sticker.
Next, there is a distance of distance.
We adjust it to the replacement degree of this piece of fabric.
We also choose the name line.
There is also a distance of distance.
We also adjust it to 2.
Let's run the rendering again.
Here, we can see that the sticker and the name line are displayed.
Here, the seal and the sign of the seal are also added.
The distance function of the distance.
Next, I'm going to introduce the text-to-text version of the editor.
Previously, people have edited text-to-text version.
can only be adjusted by inputting data.
Now, our 6.0 has launched a new feature
that can be adjusted by using 3D window or 2D window editor.
You can watch this video.
Next, I'm going to show you how to convert our virtual model into a component.
Usually, when we make clothes, there are some parts like this on it,
such as this date button.
There are two ways to make this date button.
One is to convert it into a component,
and then paste it in a fixed position,
but the component does not conflict with the panel.
The other way is to convert it into a virtual model
and conflict with the panel.
But this method is not displayed on our supply list.
Here, we have made an optimization of 6.0 for it.
I have converted this date button into a virtual model.
There is a supply list on our property editor.
The current classification is virtual model.
We convert it to a component.
This date button will be displayed on our supply list.
And this is just displayed on our supply list.
It does not change its function.
Here we can take a look at these two supply lists.
Next, I'm going to introduce you to our YKK metal preset.
Now we have added four YKK metal presets.
Here, I have added four YKK metal presets.
Let's open a file.
I choose the pull chain,
and then convert its material to metal.
Under the metal, there is a metal preset.
This is the YKK metal preset.
This pull chain is not limited to the YKK pull chain.
As long as it is in our warehouse,
we can use this YKK metal preset.
Next, I'm going to introduce you to the compatible Zynologia.
Zynologia is a Spanish company.
It is used to do the water-washing molding effect of jeans.
Through laser technology,
it can make the water-washing molding effect of jeans in a few seconds.
What is the problem with its water-washing molding effect?
The problem is that it can protect against light.
This is the problem of the Zynologia YKK metal preset.
The metal is larger than the water-washing molding effect of Zynologia.
The data received from the Síndrome of Live coolant is
less than 1.5 times the amount of the water-washing molding effect.
It is not the same as when using other materials.
When the Zymologia YKK metal preset came out in 2019,
the Batman is smaller than the Zynologia.
And the length is less than the size of the metal preset.
However, it can be used to make the water-washing molding effect of Jeanne.
As long as it is in our warehouse,
it will not matter the size of the metal preset.
Next, I would like to introduce the last part, which is the function optimization part.
The function optimization part is mainly optimized in three parts.
The first is the optimization of UI optimization and optimization of 3D functions and optimization of 2D functions.
For UI optimization, we have improved the optimization of the document window of the guide and guide,
as well as the optimization of the interface display of the object window.
Previously, it was a display of text, but now it is a display of this kind of icon.
We have also added an optimization of two 3D functions,
added a 3D layout, such as such a rectangle, cylinder, and so on,
as well as integrated the measurement and teaching tools of virtual models.
Now, our teaching tools are
Because the function of the measurement and teaching tools of virtual models has been partially recombined,
we have canceled the teaching tools of virtual models.
In addition, the teaching tools of virtual models that we previously attached to the teaching tools of virtual models
have now been changed to the measurement of virtual models.
In terms of measurement, we have added a straight line measurement.
It can measure the thickness of the model.
The last one is an optimization of our 2D function.
In the previous video, we did an extension version,
and when we were doing the extension version and the measurement,
its internal line and the basic line cannot move with water.
Now we can move with water.
You can watch a video here.
Here I choose the measurement tool,
and then set its number.
After opening, you can see that its basic line moves with water.
You can also change the measuring degree of the measurement.
And then we will use the spray tool to test it.
When we use the open tool, we can also open both sides at the same time by pressing the middle button.
Similarly, our baseline is to move along with the open tool.
Next, I will show you how to fold and save time.
Now, we can correctly create a link along the connection line.
Thank you for watching.
We have some other advantages for 2D functions.
For example, 2D measurement can be created or the connection line measurement can be made.
The fold and save tool can be used to fold the baseline, the internal line, and the panel line into 2D measurements.
Now, we can change the 2D measurement.
It can display or hide 2D measurements in the
flower distribution mode.
When moving the end point, it can enter the length of the line, and it can only be aligned
to the outside of the board before, but now it can be aligned to the inside of the board.
The above is the introduction of all the new features of our 6.0.
Thank you all.